Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 11: Boxes 636-699
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 11: Boxes 636-699
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 651, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 651, Folder 10)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 651, Folder 11)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 651, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 651, Folder 13)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 651, Folder 14)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 651, Folder 15)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 651, Folder 16)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 651, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 651, Folder 18)
- Western New York Council on Occupational Health and Safety, Publication (Box 651, Folder 19)
- Actors and Artists of America (AAA), Publication (Box 651, Folder 20)
- Actors and Artists of America (AAA), Publication (Box 651, Folder 21)
- Actors and Artists of America (AAA), Publication (Box 651, Folder 22)
- Actors and Artists of America (AAA), Publication (Box 651, Folder 23)
- Actors and Artists of America (AAA), Publication (Box 651, Folder 24)
- Actors and Artists of America (AAA), Publication (Box 651, Folder 25)
- Actors and Artists of America (AAA), Publication (Box 651, Folder 26)
- Actors and Artists of America (AAA), Publication (Box 651, Folder 27)
- Actors and Artists of America (AAA), Publication (Box 651, Folder 28)
- Airline Pilots Association (APA), Publication (Box 651, Folder 29)
- Airline Pilots Association (APA), Publication (Box 652, Folder 1)
- Air Traffic Controllers Association, Publication (Box 652, Folder 2)
- Air Traffic Controllers Association, Publication (Box 652, Folder 3)
- Allied Pilots Association, Publication (Box 652, Folder 4)
- Association for Union Democracy, Publication (Box 652, Folder 5)
- UAW, Publication (Box 652, Folder 6)
- UAW, Publication (Box 652, Folder 7)
- UAW, Publication (Box 652, Folder 8)
- UAW, Publication (Box 652, Folder 9)
- UAW, Publication (Box 652, Folder 10)
- Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union of America, Local 3, Publication (Box 652, Folder 11)
- International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Shipbuilders, Blacksmiths, Forgers, and Helpers, Publication (Box 652, Folder 12)
- BAC (International Union of Bricklayers and Allied Craftsmen), Publication (Box 652, Folder 13)
- NABET (National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians), Publication (Box 652, Folder 14)
- California State Employees, Publication (Box 652, Folder 15)
- California State Employees, Publication (Box 652, Folder 16)
- Campaign for Labor Rights, Publication (Box 652, Folder 17)
- UBC (United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America), Publication (Box 652, Folder 18)
- Central New York Coalition for Occupational Safety and Health, Publication (Box 652, Folder 19)
- Central New York Labor Agency, Publication (Box 652, Folder 20)
- CSEA, Publication (Box 652, Folder 21)
- CSEA, Publication (Box 652, Folder 22)
- ACTWU, Publication (Box 652, Folder 23)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW), Publication (Box 652, Folder 24)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW), Publication (Box 653, Folder 1)
- Communication Workers of America (CWA), Publication (Box 653, Folder 2)
- Communication Workers of America (CWA), Publication (Box 653, Folder 3)
- Cortland Workers Rights, Publication (Box 653, Folder 4)
- Culinary Workers Union, Publication (Box 653, Folder 5)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 653, Folder 6)
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 653, Folder 7)
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 653, Folder 8)
- IBEW (International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers), Publication (Box 653, Folder 9)
- Elevator Constructors, Publication (Box 653, Folder 10)
- Farm Labor Union, Publication (Box 653, Folder 11)
- United Farm Workers, Publication (Box 653, Folder 12)
- National Federation of Federal Employees, Publication (Box 653, Folder 13)
- International Association of Firefighters, Publication (Box 653, Folder 14)
- Professional Flight Attendents Asscoiation, Publication (Box 653, Folder 15)
- United Food and Commercial Workers, Publication (Box 653, Folder 16)
- United Food and Commercial Workers, Publication (Box 653, Folder 17)
- ILGWU, Publication (Box 653, Folder 18)
- Glass, Molders, Pottery, Plastics & Allied Workers (GMP) International Union, Publication (Box 653, Folder 19)
- American Flint Glass Workers Union, Publication (Box 653, Folder 20)
- American Flint Glass Workers Union, Publication (Box 653, Folder 21)
- American Federation of Government Employees, Publication (Box 653, Folder 22)
- Graphic Communications International Union, Publication (Box 653, Folder 23)
- Graphic Communications International Union, Publication (Box 653, Folder 24)
- Harvard Union of Clerical and Technical Workers, Publication (Box 653, Folder 25)
- National Union of Healthcare Workers, Publication (Box 653, Folder 26)
- International Labor Communications Association, Publication (Box 653, Folder 27)
- International Labor Communications Association, Publication (Box 653, Folder 28)
- International Labor Communications Association, Publication (Box 653, Folder 29)
- International Labor Communications Association, Publication (Box 653, Folder 30)
- Iron Workers, Publication (Box 654, Folder 1)
- Laborers' International Union of North America, Publication (Box 654, Folder 2)
- Laborers' International Union of North America, Publication (Box 654, Folder 3)
- National Association of Letter Carriers (U.S.), Publication (Box 654, Folder 4)
- National Association of Letter Carriers (U.S.), Publication (Box 654, Folder 5)
- National Association of Letter Carriers (U.S.), Publication (Box 654, Folder 6)
- National Association of Letter Carriers (U.S.), Publication (Box 654, Folder 7)
- International Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (BLE), Publication (Box 654, Folder 8)
- International Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (BLE), Publication (Box 654, Folder 9)
- International Longshoremen's Association, Publication (Box 654, Folder 10)
- International Longshoremen's Association, Publication (Box 654, Folder 11)
- International Longshoremen's Association, Publication (Box 654, Folder 12)
- International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Publication (Box 654, Folder 13)
- International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Publication (Box 654, Folder 14)
- International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Publication (Box 654, Folder 15)
- United Mine Workers of American, Publication (Box 654, Folder 16)
- United Mine Workers of American, Publication (Box 654, Folder 17)
- American Federation of Musicians, Publication (Box 654, Folder 18)
- National Consumers League, Publication (Box 654, Folder 19)
- National Consumers League, Publication (Box 654, Folder 20)
- National Consumers League, Publication (Box 654, Folder 21)
- National Education Association, Publication (Box 654, Folder 22)
- National Labor Committee, Publication (Box 654, Folder 23)
- National Labor Committee, Publication (Box 654, Folder 24)
- United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA), Publication (Box 654, Folder 25)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Publication (Box 654, Folder 26)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Publication (Box 654, Folder 27)
- IUOE (International Union of Operating Engineers), Publication (Box 654, Folder 28)
- IUOE (International Union of Operating Engineers), Publication (Box 654, Folder 29)
- Pacific Maritime Association, Publication (Box 654, Folder 30)
- Musicians of Greater New York, Publication (Box 655, Folder 1)
- Musicians of Greater New York, Publication (Box 655, Folder 2)
- Musicians of Greater New York, Publication (Box 655, Folder 3)
- Musicians of Greater New York, Publication (Box 655, Folder 4)
- Musicians of Greater New York, Publication (Box 655, Folder 5)
- Musicians of Greater New York, Publication (Box 655, Folder 6)
- International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades, Publication (Box 655, Folder 7)
- International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades, Publication (Box 655, Folder 8)
- International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades, Publication (Box 655, Folder 9)
- International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades, Publication (Box 655, Folder 10)
- Paper, Allied-Industrial, Chemical and Energy Workers, Publication (Box 655, Folder 11)
- Paper, Allied-Industrial, Chemical and Energy Workers, Publication (Box 655, Folder 12)
- Paperworkers International Union, Publication (Box 655, Folder 13)
- Paperworkers International Union, Publication (Box 655, Folder 14)
- Allied Pilots Association, Publication (Box 655, Folder 15)
- Plumbers and Pipefitters, Publication (Box 655, Folder 16)
- Plumbers and Pipefitters, Publication (Box 655, Folder 17)
- Plumbers and Pipefitters, Publication (Box 655, Folder 18)
- National Association of Postal and Federal Employees, Publication (Box 655, Folder 19)
- National Association of Postal and Federal Employees, Publication (Box 655, Folder 20)
- National Post Office Mail Handlers, Publication (Box 655, Folder 21)
- National Association of Postal Supervisors, Publication (Box 655, Folder 22)
- National Association of Postal Supervisors, Publication (Box 655, Folder 23)
- American Postal Workers Union, Publication (Box 655, Folder 24)
- American Postal Workers Union, Publication (Box 655, Folder 25)
- Professional Staff Congress, Publication (Box 656, Folder 1)
- Public Employees Federation, Publication (Box 656, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, Publication (Box 656, Folder 3)
- United Union of Roofers, Waterproofers and Allied Workers, Publication (Box 656, Folder 4)
- American Federation of School Administrators, Publication (Box 656, Folder 5)
- Seafarers' International Union, Publication (Box 656, Folder 6)
- Security, Police and Fire Professionals of America, Publication (Box 656, Folder 7)
- SEIU, Publication (Box 656, Folder 8)
- SEIU, Publication (Box 656, Folder 9)
- SEIU, Publication (Box 656, Folder 10)
- SEIU, Publication (Box 656, Folder 11)
- SEIU, Publication (Box 656, Folder 12)
- Sheet Metal Workers, Publication (Box 656, Folder 13)
- International Alliance of Theatrical Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employes and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada, Publication (Box 656, Folder 14)
- AFSCME, Publication (Box 656, Folder 15)
- AFSCME, Publication (Box 656, Folder 16)
- AFSCME, Publication (Box 656, Folder 17)
- AFSCME, Publication (Box 656, Folder 18)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 656, Folder 19)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 656, Folder 20)
- American Federation of Teachers (AFT), Publication (Box 656, Folder 21)
- American Federation of Teachers (AFT), Publication (Box 656, Folder 22)
- American Federation of Teachers (AFT), Publication (Box 656, Folder 23)
- American Federation of Teachers (AFT), Publication (Box 656, Folder 24)
- American Federation of Teachers (AFT), Publication (Box 656, Folder 25)
- American Federation of Teachers (AFT), Publication (Box 656, Folder 26)
- California Federation of Teachers, Publication (Box 656, Folder 27)
- NYSUT, Publication (Box 656, Folder 28)
- Teamsters, Publication (Box 656, Folder 29)
- NYUST, Publication (Box 657, Folder 1)
- NYUST, Publication (Box 657, Folder 2)
- NYUST, Publication (Box 657, Folder 3)
- NYUST, Publication (Box 657, Folder 4)
- Teamsters, Publication (Box 657, Folder 5)
- AFTE (American Federation of Technical Engineers), Publication (Box 657, Folder 6)
- AFTE (American Federation of Technical Engineers), Publication (Box 657, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Transit Union, Publication (Box 657, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Transit Union, Publication (Box 657, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Transit Union, Publication (Box 657, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Transit Union, Publication (Box 657, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Transit Union, Publication (Box 657, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Transit Union, Publication (Box 657, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Transit Union, Publication (Box 657, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Transit Union, Publication (Box 657, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Transit Union, Publication (Box 657, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Transit Union, Publication (Box 657, Folder 17)
- Transportation Workers of America, Publication (Box 657, Folder 18)
- Transportation Workers of America, Publication (Box 657, Folder 19)
- Transportation Communications Union, Publication (Box 658, Folder 1)
- Transportation Communications Union, Publication (Box 658, Folder 2)
- UTU (United Transportation Union), Publication (Box 658, Folder 3)
- UTU (United Transportation Union), Publication (Box 658, Folder 4)
- UTU (United Transportation Union), Publication (Box 658, Folder 5)
- UTU (United Transportation Union), Publication (Box 658, Folder 6)
- Union Plus, Publication (Box 658, Folder 7)
- United University Professionals (UUP), Publication (Box 658, Folder 8)
- United University Professionals (UUP), Publication (Box 658, Folder 9)
- United University Professionals (UUP), Publication (Box 658, Folder 10)
- Utility Workers Union of America, Publication (Box 658, Folder 11)
- Utility Workers Union of America, Publication (Box 658, Folder 12)
- UNITE, Publication (Box 658, Folder 13)
- UNITE, Publication (Box 658, Folder 14)
- UNITE, Publication (Box 658, Folder 15)
- UNITE, Publication (Box 658, Folder 16)
- UNITE, Publication (Box 658, Folder 17)
- UNITE, Publication (Box 658, Folder 18)
- UNITE, Publication (Box 658, Folder 19)
- UNITE, Publication (Box 658, Folder 20)
- UNITE, Publication (Box 658, Folder 21)
- UNITE, Publication (Box 658, Folder 22)
- UNITE, Publication (Box 658, Folder 23)
- UNITE, Publication (Box 658, Folder 24)
- UNITE, Publication (Box 658, Folder 25)
- UNITE-HERE, Publication (Box 658, Folder 26)
- UNITE-HERE, Publication (Box 658, Folder 27)
- Work In America Institute, Publication (Box 658, Folder 28)
- Woring Today, Publication (Box 658, Folder 29)
- Workmen's Circle, Publication (Box 658, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous, Publication (Box 659, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous, Publication (Box 659, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous, Publication (Box 659, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous, Publication (Box 659, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous, Publication (Box 659, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous, Publication (Box 659, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous, Publication (Box 659, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous, Publication (Box 659, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous, Publication (Box 659, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous, Publication (Box 659, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous, Publication (Box 659, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous, Publication (Box 659, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous, Publication (Box 659, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous, Publication (Box 659, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous, Publication (Box 659, Folder 15)
- TWUA, Publication (Box 660, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Cope-Legislative Activity Manual, 1974; Publication (Box 660, Folder 1)
    Author: Bruce Dunton, Bruce Raynor
    Notes: March 18-23, 1974
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 660, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: National Health Security Speaker's Manual, Publication (Box 660, Folder 2)
- International Alliance of Theatrical Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employes and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada, Publication (Box 660, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Report of the General Secretary - Treasurer, 1966-1968 (Box 660, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Publication (Box 660, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Financial Statements, 1966-1967 (Box 660, Folder 4)
- ACWA, AFL-CIO, CLC, Publication (Box 660, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A Manual for Organizers, Publication (Box 660, Folder 5)
    Author: Ed Blair
- AFL-CIO Cope, Publication (Box 660, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: How to Win Handbook for Political Education, Publication (Box 660, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Biennial Report, 1954-1955 (Box 660, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Twenty Year Report, 1948-1968 (Box 660, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: The First Ten Years, 1948-1957 (Box 660, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Fifteen Year Report, 1948-1963 (Box 660, Folder 6)
  - 1948-1963 (Box 660, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 660, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Why Unions?, Publication (Box 660, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Financing the Schools, Publication (Box 660, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: This is the AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 660, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Collective Bargaining Democracy on the Job, Publication (Box 660, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Agreement and Plan of Merger and Consolidation, Publication (Box 660, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Unemployment Insurance Benefits for Workers in New York State, 1959-1960 (Box 660, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Can We Keep The Schools From Sinking?, Publication (Box 660, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: The Growing Burdens of Medical Costs, Publication (Box 660, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Ammunition Jobs Not Promises, 1977; Publication (Box 660, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Who is the Imperialist?, Publication (Box 660, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Stewards Witness Report, Publication (Box 660, Folder 7)
    Notes: Blank
  - Item 12: Rules of the National Union of Tailors and Garment Workers, Publication (Box 660, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Rules of the International Textile, Garment & Leather Workers' Federation, Publication (Box 660, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Agreement and Plan of Merger and Consolidation, Publication (Box 660, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 660, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Officers' Guide, Publication (Box 660, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Sixth Montana State Union Meeting, 1931; Publication (Box 660, Folder 8)
    Notes: September 3
  - Item 3: Report Board of International Trustees and International Secretary-Treasurer Raymond Majerus, 1982; Publication (Box 660, Folder 8)
    Author: Clarence H. Johnson
    Notes: January 1 - December 31
  - Item 4: Steward Handbook, Publication (Box 660, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Steward's Guide, Publication (Box 660, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: The Safety Sentinel, Publication (Box 660, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Stewards Handbook, Publication (Box 660, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Steward's Grievance Guide, Publication (Box 660, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Pocket Guide for Shop Stewards, Publication (Box 660, Folder 8)
  - Publication (Box 660, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: A Union Ahead of its Time, Publication (Box 660, Folder 8)
  - Publication (Box 660, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 660, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 660, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 660, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Group Insurance Plan for Retail and Department Store Employees, 1969; Publication (Box 660, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 660, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Midwest News, Publication (Box 660, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: The Garment Worker, 1977; Publication (Box 660, Folder 9)
    Notes: June
  - Item 7: UMWA Journal, Publication (Box 660, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Viewpoint, 1978; Publication (Box 660, Folder 9)
    Notes: Vol. 8, No. 2, Second Quarter
  - Item 9: Midwest News, Publication (Box 660, Folder 9)
    Notes: Vol. 10, No. 2, June
  - Item 10: Action, 1977; Publication (Box 660, Folder 9)
    Notes: April/May
  - Item 11: Memo Cope, 1978; Publication (Box 660, Folder 9)
    Notes: August 14
  - Item 12: CWA News, 1978; Publication (Box 660, Folder 9)
    Notes: August
  - Item 13: The international Teamster, 1978; Publication (Box 660, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: Audit Report Period, 1975; Publication (Box 660, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: Solidarity, 1978; Publication (Box 660, Folder 9)
    Notes: Vol. 21, No. 7, June
  - Item 16: Federationist, Publication (Box 660, Folder 9)
    Notes: November
  - Publication (Box 660, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 660, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Comparative Survey of Major CBAs, 1974; Publication (Box 660, Folder 10)
- Cornell University, Publication (Box 660, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Cornell University Arbitraation institute A joint educational project, Publication (Box 660, Folder 11)
- ACWA, Publication (Box 660, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Sidney Hillman Health Center of Rochester Medical Arts Building, Publication (Box 660, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Progress Through Pioneering, Publication (Box 660, Folder 12)
    Notes: Union Center, Pennsylvania Joint Board
  - Item 3: Welcome To Your Union, Publication (Box 660, Folder 12)
  - Publication (Box 660, Folder 12)
- UNITE, Publication (Box 660, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Why Unions Are In Politics, 1998; Publication (Box 660, Folder 13)
    Author: Harry Kelber
  - Item 2: Why Unions Are Good for You and Your Family, 1998; Publication (Box 660, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Uniform Justice, Publication (Box 660, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: The Making of Ideal Union Leaders, 1998; Publication (Box 660, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: The Making of Ideal Union Members, 1998; Publication (Box 660, Folder 13)
- UNITE, Publication (Box 660, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Code of Conduct: Safeguarding standards or shielding abuses?, Publication (Box 660, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Compromising on Quality Conditions at Angelica Textile Services Jeopardize Hospital Linen Quality, Publication (Box 660, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Time is Money, Publication (Box 660, Folder 14)
    Author: John Lund, Ph.D
- ILGWU, Publication (Box 660, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: From "Justice", 1947-1950 (Box 660, Folder 15)
    Author: Bernard Seaman
- UERMWA, Publication (Box 660, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: So Long, Partner!, Publication (Box 660, Folder 16)
    Author: Fred Wright
  - Publication (Box 660, Folder 16)
- The National Labor Committee, Publication (Box 660, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Free Trade's Hidden Secrets, Publication (Box 660, Folder 17)
- Justice vs J.P. Stevens Testimony, Publication (Box 660, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Justice vs J.P. Stevens Testimony, Publication (Box 660, Folder 18)
- On the Job, Publication (Box 660, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: On the Job, 1976; Publication (Box 660, Folder 19)
- UNITE!, Publication (Box 660, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Teaching Resources on Sweatshops & Child Labor, Publication (Box 660, Folder 20)
- Suiting Everyone: The Democratization of Clothing in America, Publication (Box 660, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Suiting Everyone: The Democratization of Clothing in America, Publication (Box 660, Folder 21)
- US Department of Labor, Publication (Box 660, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The American Worker, Publication (Box 660, Folder 22)
    Author: Richard B. Morris
- International Union, UAW, Publication (Box 660, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: We Make Our Own History A Portrait of the UAW, 1986; Publication (Box 660, Folder 23)
- ACTWU, Publication (Box 660, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: The Clothes Off Our Back, 1995; Publication (Box 660, Folder 24)
    Author: Debra Lindsay
    Notes: A History of ACTWU 459
- ACWA, Publication (Box 660, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: The Amalgamated Illustrated Almanac, 1924; Publication (Box 660, Folder 25)
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 660, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Centennial Anthology, 1981; Publication (Box 660, Folder 26)
- William Cahn, Publication (Box 660, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Lawrence 1912 The Bread & Roses Strike, 1977; Publication (Box 660, Folder 27)
    Author: William Cahn
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 660, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: The Paul F. Cole Building Dedication, 2011; Publication (Box 660, Folder 28)
- Order of Railway Conductores, Publication (Box 660, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Order of Railway Conductores, 1909; Publication (Box 660, Folder 29)
- Is Colorado in America?, Publication (Box 660, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Is Colorado in America?, Publication (Box 660, Folder 30)
- Official Proceedings - 4th Regular United Food & Commercial Workers International Union Convention - July 27-31, 1998 (Chicago, Illinois), Publication (Box 661)
- International Association of Machinists, Publication (Box 662, Folder 1)
- Switchmen's Union of North America, Publication (Box 662, Folder 2)
- Switchmen's Union of North America, Publication (Box 662, Folder 3)